Visit turkision.com for more!
Gonca, come. My Gonca.
You'll be fine.
Here, who are you?!
You won't get away now! I will kill you!
Gonca, Gonca!
My Gonca. My gazelle-eyed.
My gazelle-eyed, you will be alright.
Alaeddin. I need to go.
I need to go. My brother.,
my brother would kill me.
Gonca! Gonca open your eyes!
Open your gazelle eyes! Get
up, come on you will be alright!
You will be alright my Gonca!
The decision has been made.
There is no turning back nor time left.
Before Tajeddin Noyan's army moves..
..we will quickly go to the
encampment and strike them.
-Orhan Bey.
-My Bey.
You will cover the left wing.
As you command, Osman Bey.
-Gunduz Bey, you will cover the right wing.
-Sure, Osman Bey.
Even if we break Tajeddin Noyan's army..
..Olcaytu Khan’s army will come.
It is his nephew, Bey. He
will want to have us pay.
Tajeddin Noyan has a lot to pay for, Boran Bey.
However, we will think about it later.
No. Do not worry.
We will make a move for him now. However..
We won't be alone in this.
Of course, those with a burning
heart for war must be with us.
It is a hard job, Osman Bey.
Those who are tough can walk on the hard path.
Do not worry. We will win with Allah's permission.
-If Allah permits.
-However..
..the enemy does not march only from the east.
Now, the executioner of Rome
is about to come to our lands.
-Bayindir Bey.
-My Bey.
Go to the lords.
Be sure again..
..that they won’t bow down to anyone but us.
All of them will pay their taxes for this union.
Do not worry, my Osman
Bey. I can have their loyalty..
..and the tax by force if needed, for sure.
For sure. We will make our moves now..
..however, the enemy won't just stand around.
If we can't strike Tajeddin Noyan's
army, then he will come to Yenisehir.
Bala Hatun. Take the kids and elderly..
...and get them out of the city before dawn.
Take them to the cave on the road to Kocakulak.
As you command, my Bey. We will take precautions.
-Are we allowed, my Bey?
-Come in.
Alaeddin? What happened, son?
-My son?
-A hatun..
..tried to kill me with this.
A Tatar crossbow.
And a Hatun..
Are you alright?
I am alright, my Bey.
They hit Yakup Bey first..
..now they hit you.
TACETTIN NOYAN HEADQUARTERS
So you're here. The war has started, Mehmed Bey.
Seeing you by my side brought me joy.
Osman crossed the line. He
will pay for what he has done.
He will. We will make him pay together.
However, I want you to do something.
I want to see Osman at Frontier
Marketplace for the last time.
You will be a intermediary for that meeting.
You're telling me the war has
started, and you still want to see him.
-Why, Tajeddin Noyan?
-Because..
..having Osman begging at my
feet brings more joy than his death.
I have such a card in my hand..
.Osman will bow down to me sooner or later.
Don’t you want this as well?
This move makes Germiyanids enemies to Kayis.
However, anything is worth seeing Osman bow down.
You are on the right way,
Mehmed Bey. You will live long.
How will I do this?
My Allah, grant her healing.
No, a wooden spoon. A wooden spoon..
Hold on my Gonca.
Hold on, you are strong..
In the name of Allah, the merciful,
the compassionate.
The Healer! The Healer! The Healer!
We checked with the ladies, my Bey.
That Hatun is not Mongol.
She is Christian.
These are her clothes.
Similar to what we saw today.
That is the arrow shot Yakup Bey..
..and these are the arrows we
found on her, they are the same.
The arrows match.
They are the same, however,
I feel something is wrong.
This is a Tatar crossbow. This
is not a crusader made bow.
They tried to do Mongol artisanship.
However, look at the string.
Crusaders use silk for strings, my Bey.
This is Mongol string. Made from intestines.
Intestines you say..
They tried to frame Mongol
crossbow as crusader-made, is that so?
Are they playing tricks on us, my Bey?
It seems they're trying to confuse us.
First, Yakup Bey. Then, Alaeddin..
This issue will be a big one.
They didn't think we would find her,
they only thought we would find the arrow.
Now, we have a Tatar crossbow.
According to them, we were going
to hold Mongols responsible..
It is someone who tries to ensure our aim, my Bey.
This could only benefit the Executioner of Rome.
The gorgeous Princess Maria.
Finally, we've met. The unity
of llhanids and Byzantine..
..will be realized thanks to our wedding.
This is a very important matter.
I am aware, Tajeddin Noyan.
And I am quite happy for it.
You can be sure that I will
be a loyal partner to you.
Everything for the well-being of the two states.
-Kanyumaz.
-My Bey.
Go to Yenisehir and send word to Osman.
Tajeddin Noyan wants to
talk with Osman in our tribe.
-His intention is to make peace.
-As you command, my Bey.
Send word to Cerkutay. Tell him
to prepare Frontier Marketplace.
I want a welcoming that deserves
someone like Tajeddin Noyan.
Who is this? Do you know, Kanyumaz?
I don't, my Bey. He is a stranger.
Princess Maria. How good it is to see you.
congratulate you again.
You didn’t come here to just
congratulate, right Imren “Pegin?
I've heard what happened with
Osman. I told you, Tajeddin Noyan..
..Osman would never bow to you.
Neither in a cage nor in a forest.
You only lost time.
Now, you do not have
any other option but to fight.
We tried the way of peace first.
The wrath of merciful men..
..are greater than their mercy, Imren Tegin.
Soon, you will witness a big bloodbath.
I will take Osman's life in Yakup's tribe.
And that stupid son of his..
..will serve me without knowing.
Then, we will make that..
..grand wedding with Princess Maria.
Until then, you will wait for me
at the palace in Konya, Princess.
Now, it is time to go.
When we get rid of Osman..
..our wedding will have more meaning.
I will wait for you with patience, Tajeddin Noyan.
You know what they say, ’’May
Allah unites you two together”, Noyan.
Osman's death benefits me the most.
-If you need help..
-There is no need.
I don't want mercenaries at my side.
Alright. I hope you will
be enough to do all of that.
Tajeddin Noyan.
Tajeddin tricked Mehmed Bey.
They will kill Osman Bey at Yakup Bey's tribe.
They set up a trap, let him know.
Come on!
Now we'll go to hit Tajedding
Noyan's army quickly.
Everybody knows well what
to do. Our target is his tent.
After we take Tajeddin's head, we will
figure out what to do with his headless army.
Osman Bey, I got a message from my alps.
They're on the way. I wish we could wait for them.
If we had the Kayi warri the Kayi warriors
of the east, we would be stronger in fight.
No, Gunduz Bey. What if
Tajeddin Noyan's army comes..
...by the time we wait for your alps?
We'd be a thousand more but
they'd be ten thousands more then.
I can't take that risk. We will
attack Tajeddin Noyan's army today.
Osman Bey, I’ve brought a message from Mehmed Bey.
-What is it?
-Tajeddin Noya
..wants to negotiate with you in the frontier
market with Mehmed Bey as the reconciler.
A last meeting for peace, Osman Bey.
Tell Mehmed Bey...
-I'll let him know my decision tonight.
-As you order, Osman Bey.
Osman Bey, don't you go there
-That dog is laying a trap.
-Don't worry, Gunduz Bey.
Don’t worry.
If I were sure, I'd say we would be there.
Of course, he is trying to lay a trap.
My Bey, we got a message, from Princess Maria.
Tajeddin Noyan's invitation is a trap.
Two
Well... Now I'm sure.
Yet something bothers my mind.
Is Mehmed Bey involved in this trap?
He deceived him. He thinks he’ll really negotiate.
I'd never rather kill my own kin.
Well, Gunduz Bey... We were going to hunt.
But the hunt is coming to me now.
Songur Agha, go to Tajeddin
Noyan's prisoner camp with your alps.
While we take his head in the frontier
market, you’ll save the prisoners.
As you order, my Bey.
Let's go, alps!
-Bayindir Bey.
-My Bey.
We'll keep the promise we gave Princess Maria.
Before we go to Atronos, set her free.
Consider it done, my Bey.
I will make Princess come together with her lover.
Thank you. Boran
Send the fastest horse to the
frontier market. Let Cerkutay know.
-Tell him to prepare all the alps.
-As my Bey orders.
We're making a move but
we should still be cautious.
Alaaddin and his alps will protect the palace.
Come on, alps!
Everybody on horses!
We will cut off Tajeddin Noyan's head today.
Gunduz Bey
You aren't going to kill that
dog without me, are you?
We have an account to settle.
They're from Hayme Mother's blood. I
wouldn't expect them to do otherwise.
Come on!
-Come on!
-Giddap!
-My Shahzade.
-Baysungur, what is the situation?
The same, my Shahzade.
Ulgen Hatun is working inside.
Baysungur, I'm here. You go.
Let me know if anybody calls me.
-Come on.
-Let's go.
I'm here, Gonca.
-This is not working. Her fever isn’t going down
-Hold on, Gonca.
You'll fere alright.
You will be alright.
My Shahzade, we should
talk to Bala Hatun at least.
No, Ulgen Hatun. Neither of my parents will know.
I came here at the cost of
my life despite my brother.
Although I know he'll kill me.
If they find out,
...they will send Gonca to
Mehmed. And Mehmed will kill her.
Alaaddin...
I'm here. I'm here.
You'll be alright.
In the name of Allah, the merciful,
the compassionate.
We need ice. Keep applying vinegar on her.
I'll go send some alps to find cure.
Mother, it's me!
he sees Gonca, we can’t stop him.
We can't let Ghazi, Ulgen Hatun. If
he sees Gonca, we can't stop him.
Mother, it's me. Why is this door stuck?
-What will we do?
Don’t push the door. I’m sick.
Open the door then; Let me check
you. I'm supposed to look after you.
No, I can't! It's contagious.
Go away! And do come back until I recover.
Since my father left, she's got worse. My Allah...
He's gone.
Alaaddin isn't dead, huh?
Osman will get suspicious.
We will meet very soon.
But I will be the one pulling
the strings in the meeting.
I will kill...
...emperor's beloved pretty
daughter Princess Maria...
...and put the blame on Osman.
What about Tajeddin Noyan?
The emperor will declare war against
Osman for killing his daughter...
...and against Mongolians
for failing to protect her.
And I'll be the only ruler in
these lands during the chaos.
And you’ll be the servants of this power.
Benjamin, the route? Daniel,
did you lay traps on the road?
Levi, are the soldiers to destroy
Mongolian convoy going to Konya ready?
Good.
You look like you gained a victory, Imren Tegin.
I will. So you will.
For a long time, we've been only losing.
Roman Lords are paying taxes to a Turk.
One of Osman’s Beys, Bayindir.
He's coming to collect taxes tomorrow.
He'll come to collect taxes and deliver his life.
Don't. Imren Tegin.
If you harm Osman's man, you'll
draw him over you completely.
Emperor sent me here to destroy Osman.
I'll separate him from his
pack and draw him to me.
And with only one move, I
will wipe his name off the world.
I mean... That’s already what I want, Olivia.
Benjamin, Daniel, Levi. We are going.
-Where are we going now?
-To reinforce the alliance of Rome and Mongolians.
GERMIYANOGLU BORDER - FRONTIER MARKET
Come here, dastard.
Your death is awaiting you inside.
Welcome, Tajeddin Noyan.
-Thank you.
Welcome.
Tajeddin Noyan.
-An eye for an eye, huh, Osman Bey?
-Not yet.
The retaliation is not over yet.
What are you doing here? Osman Bey?
I invited you for peace. But you
are using my tent for your revenge.
Peace is made with honorable people.
Not with dishonourable people like him.
You wanted to kill me.
You used Mehmet for this.
But... I learned that
beforehand and took precautions.
Osman Bey is right, Mehmet Bey.
My intention is to kill him here...
...and stop him from injuring the Alps.
He is the head of the rebels.
You wanted to kill me.
You used Mehmet. You wanted
to turn brothers into enemies.
But I informed Alps beforehand..
...and took precautions.
Is Osman Bey telling the truth, Tajeddin?
Do you think you can stop me?
Besides... how do you know?
Princess Maria, who was going to be your...
...Hatun, told us everything.
What happened, Tajeddin Noyan?
You were going for hunting,
but now you became the prey.
Stop there.
Where are you going, huh
Where are you going, huh?
-Trap!
-Alps!
Allah is the Greatest!
Death is haram for me before I take my people's
revenge from you! Come at me, dastards!
Close the doors!
Let him run! We have the owner
of the dog. We will catch him for sure.
Ayse Hatun!
Until today, we didn't have a Bey's son behind us.
Don’t worry, we know how to defend ourselves.
If I hadn’t arrived on time, I would
have seen what you do and don't know.
What did you gain by...
...trapping me here, Osman Bey?
Do you think you can shed the
blood of the llkhanate dynasty?
Just as you couldn't do anything to Geyhatu
back then ...
...you won't be able to
do anything to me either, Osman Bey.
What will belonging to the
dynasty of Olcaytu Khan...
...change after all you've done?
Do you think you can escape?
I called you for peace, but
you involved me in your fight.
I will hold you
accountable for this.
The one you should hold
accountable is standing before you.
But he won't be able to leave here.
Do you want to face Mongols who conquered China...
...India, and Anatolia by killing me, huh?
Your dreams bigger than
yourself will be destroyed.
You can only be our servants.
For each drop of my blood, a thousand
men of yours will die, Osman Bey.
Is that so, huh?
Don’t you dare Osman Bey...
Stop there...
Stop there... You can't even imagine..
...the things I dare.
Now...
I will bury you, your heirs...
...and the dogs that cause fitna and follow you...
...all in these lands.
Don’t you do that... Don't you do that!
Your power...
...is nothing against my will.
You wash blood with blood, Osman.
Is that so?
Then you should know, too much blood will be shed.
Too much blood will be washed with blood.
My Bey... Thanks to Allah, we took
all the nokers down at the marketplace.
Thank you, thank you.
You did all those things...
But... you will still die under my sword.
Worse things will happen to you, Osman.
The horses coming for revenge
will trample your homeland.
For years, there will be
no crops, no flowing waters.
You are nothing now, Osman!
You are neither the first nor...
...the last to say this to us.
But as you say that we are going to be destroyed..
...we will always exist!
Stand up...
Those properties which belong to you
now will be ours soon with Allah’s consent.
Your sultanate of cruelty will be destroyed.
We will crush all the unrest you caused...
...and establish this state.
Long live Osman Bey!
I thought you were smart,
that’s why I came for peace.
But you...
...are a dreamer who has impossible dreams!
If you ignore the truth..
...you will think it is not real for sure.
This plane tree will rise slowly, gradually.
Tajeddin Noyan, when you can’t see the sun...
...you'll understand how great the state is.
This sun will burn you!
The llkhanate will make you live in hell.
All of you will die!
You will disappear under Osman's dreams!
You have oppressed us, Tajeddin Noyan.
This is really salvation for you.
The revenge of my mother
and my brother will be taken...
...now I won’t worry about anything even if I die.
My husband's murderer,
dog... You will die like a dog.
No one will disappear because of those dreams.
But you..
You and those like you...
...you will all disappear.
We will always be here!
When they come to take
their revenge... ill always be
...we will always be the wall
that protects our people!
Like a clenched fist, we will
always fight for the glorification...
...of the word of Allah
and the order of the world!
Now tell me... Will you be with me...
...in this cause of existing here?
We will!
-Will you?
-We will!
Praise be!
My Bey... The captives from Gunduz Bey's tribe
bum were saved. They are coming to Yenisehir.
So you are saying we have good news. Gunduz Bey!
All prisoners at the headquarters were
saved. They are coming to Yenisehir.
You gave me the good news
after taking Tajeddin's head...
...thank you, thank you, Osman Bey!
Thank you. Now two Kayis will unite in Yenisehir.
And when we unite, we will be
the wrist which cannot be defeated.
It wouldn’t suit us otherwise.
-Boran.
-My Bey.
Alps will be after Noyan's helper Abdulkasim.
-We have many things to learn from him.
-Yes my Bey..
Put that dog’s head..
...on a magnificent tray
and show it to all tribes..
Show it, then all the tribes
will hear about our victory.
It's time to instill trust in
friends and fear in enemies.
Long live Osman Bey!
We'll take the princess without
being seen by these dogs.
No one will be able to blame us for this.
Come on... Alps!
You will protect us.
Princess! -Bayindir Bey!
-I came to save you from these dogs. Come on.
Who are they, Bayindir Bey?
Apparently... there are
others who want the Princess.
We have no time to learn. Come on. Come on.
Where is the Princess?
In the cart.
Osman!
What are we going to do now?
This changed my plans.
Send news to the Emperor. Osman...
...killed his
dear daughter Princess Maria.
Alps will take you to Konya, to your beloved one.
My Osman Bey prepared everything.
I am grateful! May God protect
you and give power to Osman Bey.
If Allah permits.
Alps... Apparently...
...there are other people after the Princess.
Be careful.
-Yes my Bey.
Go now.
Come here. Send news to Osman Bey.
We took the Princess safely. Go.
-Kara Ali.
-My Bey.
We are going to Atranos. Come oni
Long live Osman Bey!
Bala.
-Son.
-May your victory be blessed, my Bey.
-Thank you.
-Tajeddin got the death he deserved.
-He vanished before his evil spread.
-Yes.
We cut off his head with his evil soul.
Well, there comes good after every evil.
It brought our brothers to us.
Bala Hatun, prepare good meals for
us in honor of getting rid of this trouble.
So we can strengthen our brotherhood.
Thank you, Osman Bey.
The dog called Tajeddin standing
against our unity has been eliminated.
Now can be more united and stronger.
For sure, we will.
Not only Kayi people but also everybody...
...breathed a sigh of relief with his death.
Thanks to Allah.
-Thanks to Allah.
-Come on then. Let's go.
Well... Our lands in the west are quite fertile,
...safe and close to the water. For this reason,
...you can settle in here with your tribe.
No, Osman Bey. I know you're trying to protect me.
But I want to pay off.
I want the farthest land in the east.
So I can fight first when Mongolians come.
No.
You have nothing to pay for.
Brothers are no burdens for each ether.
You can settle in here if you like. But...
..I still want you beside me in Yenisehir.
With pleasure, Osman Bey.
So... Tell me.
’’Fight never waits. Where are we marching next?
Our target is always the same.
Bursa on one side.
And Iznik on the other.
The enemy will do their best
to stop us from capturing them.
But, with Allah’s will, our
dreams are going to con true.
The way to rule the whole world...
...is going through Bursa.
It snows for 40 days.
But we hunt one day.
With Allah's will, Bursa will
also be conquered one day.
Tell me.
You are lost in thoughts. What is in your mind?
What can it be, Osman Bey?
Apart from the unity and welfare of
Kayi people, what can I think about?
I share your dreams now.
When your draw your sword,
...our swords will be drawn too.
Thank you, thank you, thank you.
Thank you, Gunduz Bey.
Thank you, Osman Bey.
Thanks to Allah, we got rid of this trouble too.
Osman Bey and his house
o played a great part in this.
Yes.
Both their women and men are so brave.
Especially what they did during your
absence. Their help was priceless.
Well... Orhan Bey... I first saw him with you.
He helped a lot, didn't he?
Thankfully. He looks like a
benevolent and good man.
He is also very brave.
He is. Praise be. May Allah help him, though.
The woman he loves is a Lord's daughter.
I saw her. She's beautiful.
It doesn't matter. Nothing can
stand against him if he loves her.
-May Allah help them come together.
-Yes.
Hope the best.
Thank you, Bala Hatun. It's like a true feast.
Thank you, Bala Hatun. It’s like a true feast.
It's a feast, in fact an important
day for you, Ayca Hatun.
Yes. My hatun, my brave son..
...and the martyrs have been avenged.
Well, everybody is here. Welcome.
Fatma Hatun, look who is here.
-Good evening.
-Mother.
-Didn't you go?
-I delayed my journey for an important duty.
-Son.
-Mother.
-Welcome, mother.
-Thanks.
Come on.
Where have you been? You keep disappearing.
Let's get started.
Well, Gunduz Bey. Welcome again.
We defeated the enemy.
You're free now. Tell me.
-When will your tribe come?
-With Allah's will,
...they'll be here soon, Osman Bey.
Then, it'll be a great day for Kayi.
A dream will come true.
Kayi will get united again.
I hope so, I hope so.
We're getting united now.
We're becoming a huge family.
Then, reveal your secrets.
Tell me about what you are hiding.
Osman Bey, you never fail to see.
That’s what I was going to talk about.
Tajeddin Noyan is dead. So we
don’t have to keep this secret anymore.
Ayca Hatun..
...is my daughter-in-law who my
martyr son trusted me to look after.
Efendize Elcim is my daughter.
Why did you do such a thing, Gunduz Bey?
Olcaytu Khan used to make daughters
of Beys marry his commanders...
...to keep beylics in order and make them obey.
When they raided our tribe to take Elcim,
...my daughter-in-law Ayca played such a game.
GERMIYANOGLU BORDER - FRONTIER MARKET
What do you mean you can't find
her, Kanyumaz? Where is Gonca?
She's gone, Mehmed Bey. We
looked everywhere but couldn't find her.
Gonca... Gonca... Keep looking
then. There must be a trail;
Gonca... If anything happens to Gonca,
...will burn the frontiers! I
will burn the frontiers in flames!
Aren't we supposed to let
Yakup Bey know, Mehmed Bey?
Yes, we are.
Shall we also tell him...
...how Osman Bey became a hero in our market?
Never. My father will never know,
find Cerkutay. Now go sister, my
Whatever you order.
I'll first find my sister.
Then I'll show everyone who
Germiyanoglu Mehmed Bey is.
-Kanyumaz.
-My Bey.
Tell alps to put the merchants in order.
Crying out for Osman Bey in my market?
-They’ll all know there is a price for that.
-As you order, my Bey.
Gonca..
Mehmed Bey, Imren Tegin is here.
He wants to see you on behalf of Byzantine.
Imren Tegin? What would he do here?
Let him in.
Germiyanoglu Mehmed Bey.
I wanted to see you on your chair in your tent.
While you were Byzantine's nightmare,
why did the emperor send you here?
You're asking what such a great
man would do in your tent. Right.
What do you want?
-Trade.
I want to trade with you.
Germiyanoglu Mehmed Bey.
What made you think that I'd
accept this offer, Imren Tegin?
Because I can see your desire for
power which is eating your brains out.
I saw you in Tajeddin Noyan's headquarters.
I know on which side you are and
who you are holding a grudge against.
And you will know about me.
Our arrows are pointed towards
the same target. If you work with me,
...you will always hit the target.
And you will have the power you are dreaming of.
Consider.
Well, that's it. Thanks to Ayca,
I didn't give my daughter to Mongolians.
But you could have told us
about it when you came here.
Why did you keep this secret for so long?
You're right, Bala Hatun. We
haven't got rid of the trouble yet.
Tajeddin Noyan may be dead
but Olcaytu still has the throne.
He will knock on my door sooner or later.
Don’t worry. They'll be only welcomed
with our swords when they come to our door.
When we are united, nobody can beat us.
We won't let anyone harm our
children. We are united now.
You're right.
That's what I want.
As two Kayi tribes are united now,
...we should crown this unity with a wedding.
Gunduz Bey...
-Speak plainly.
-Osman Bey.
I am a grand Bey with many followers.
Since I am under your protection,
I am under your command.
Since I am under your command, it means
I have to give up on many things.
Fame, reputation..
To not let that happen..
..you know what to do, Osman Bey
Tell me what you mean, Gunduz Bey.
To protect my reputation..
..I want to unite our tribes with a wedding.
For the good of our unity and my daughter..
..I want my daughter Elcim..
..to marry your bigger son, Shahzade Orhan.
What are you saying, father?
The wedding ceremony
is an important matter.
This was very sudden.
Let me speak with my house.
You should speak with yours as well.
Okay, Osman Bey.
Orhan, I risked everything.
Please save me from this
sinister castle I got trapped in.
I can not handle wars and
being without you anymore.
I want to learn Islam to become a muslim as well.
Just give me some time.
The one who loves you the most, your Holofira.
You've heard Gunduz Bey.
What do you say about this? Orhan?
My Bey, you know what goes through my head..
..and through my heart. However, this matter..
..is quite sudden for me, my Bey.
What do you say, Malhun?
Elcim looks like a good girl, my Bey.
She is one of us. From our roots.
It is a bride that everyone would want.
However..
..Orhan makes the last decision.
His mother will support him,
no matter what he decides.
Alright, alright, alright. Look, son.
I know, these are hard decisions.
However, know this..
..this is not a matter of hearts.
This is a state matter.
The unity of two tribes will
benefit everyone of course.
For the future of the state,
this will be good for us.
My son. I can not push you to make that decision.
You will make the right decision.
-Father..
-Look...
...it is easy to dream of the state,
however, carrying this burden..
..is the real matter.
Now, have some time.
-Go and think about it.
-Thank you, my Bey.
Do not worry, my Bey.
My Orhan will make the right decision.
He will. However, think about it sometimes..
It is harder to be a father than to be a bey.
I see that, being a father is harder.
My Shahzade,she is still burning up.
Ice will work, if Allah permits.
Gonca. Gonca, hold on.
Hold on Gonca. Do not let go.
My Shahzade, what if something happens to her?
May Allah protect her, what
if she doesn't make it out?
Then what will we do? Maybe we shouldn't hide her.
No, nothing will happen to her.
Nothing will happen to her. She is strong.
She is very strong.
She will be on her feet.
She is just tired.
However, she will be alright.
Go change the rag.
What did I do to my mother?
She does not allow me in.
She says she is sick. I am scared, Mother Bala.
Do not be, my valiant. Mothers are strong.
Nothing will happen to her. We will make
a soup for her, then she will be alright.
She will be good, right? Mothers are strong.
She is entrusted with me from my
father. I promised taking care of her.
Do not worry, nothing will happen.
My Shahzade, Bala Hatun is coming.
Now we are done fori
Bala Hatun will kill mei
-She will kill me!
-lllgen Hatun!
Stop.
Baysungur, what are you doing here?
Bala Hatun, I... My Shahzade..
..prepared medicine for Ulgen Hatun.
-I gave her that.
-Did Alaeddin check on her?
-What is wrong with her?
-She does not allow me in!
Mother! I can take care of you!
I don't know what is wrong with her.
my Shahzade told me to not let anyone in.
What is it I wonder.
Bala Hatun, heb says it is contagious.
Maybe do not go in.
Baysungur, let me see with my own eyes.
Ulgen?
Are you alright?
-Mother, what happened to you?
-Bala Hatun?
Do not come in, my son. I am very sick.
I am very.. It is contagious.
So Alaeddin checked on you. What did he say?
-What is wrong with you?
-He did, prepare a medicine.
He told me to rest a bit and it will pass.
It is contagious! Don't get near!
You entrusted with me. Of
course I will take care of you.
My son, I am telling you, it is contagious.
How will you take care of me if you get sick?
She is right. Shahzade Alaeddin will heal her.
Now, tonight you can stay
at Shahzade Alaeddin’s room.
The room of Shahzade Alaeddin.
Let me think about it. However,
what will happen to mother?
Shahzade Alaeddin will heal her. Do not worry.
Take good care of my mother.
Do not worry. Baysungur.
Put two baciyan on the door to
report Ulgen's condition to me.
Yeni Cazibe Noktasi As you command, Bala Hatun.
As you command, Bala Hatun.
Ulgen, you want 33 something, say it to the girls.
Ulgen, if you want something, say it to the girls.
Thank you.
Gonca... Gonca. Gonca.
I keep telling lies!
Bala Hatun will burn me!
I also burden you with a great responsibility,
but you must understand me as well.
We cannot tell anyone the truth, Ulgen Hatun.
We must protect Gonca from Mehmet, her brother.
This burden is my duty, my Shahzade.
I owe a lot to you and to her.
It's okay.
Father... don't do this to
me. Do not want this from me.
I am Kayi Bey Gunduz.
Elcim... If I bow down to Osman...
...will lose all my reputation. But...
...if this marriage happens...
...Osman and I will be equal.
Besides, you will be the
daughter-in-law in Osman Bey's family.
-You should be happy...
-Never!
I will not marry that man who loves another Hatun!
-What are you saying?
-Father...
...Orhan Bey loves another Hatun.
You don't have the option to choose, Elcim.
You will marry Orhan Bey,
You will do this for our Beylic.
Don't you worry about my honour, father?
Everyone knows Orhan Bey loves another woman.
-I will not marry a man who does not want me!
-Enough!
Since when have you been
raising your voice to your father?
Look... I lost your
mother and your brother.
I only have you left. You
are the only one I can trust.
And you will do this for us.
This marriage will happen as soon as possible.
Father... If my
mother was alive...
...she would never let this happen.
You are making me feel my motherlessness
with what you deem appropriate, father.
If your mother was here, she would also want this.
You are Efendize Elcim Hatun.
You are from Kayi tribe,
from Hayme mother's lineage.
Now... you will do what suits you...
...and you will marry Hayme
mother's grandson Orhan Bey.
But... Osman Bey will
first ask for your permission.
I know that you are going to
give the best answer for our family.
Holofira...
I broke your heart like this necklace, Holofira.
I couldn’t protect you, I
couldn’t protect my love.
Now if I...
...give up on everything...
...if I give up on Bey Orhan, Shahzade Orhan...
...if I leave everything, free
myself and come to you...
I cannot do that.
I grew up with this dream.
I swore to spill every drop of
my blood for my father’s dreams...
...for the glorification of...
...the word of Allah.
But I wanted to...
...walk this path with you.
I wanted to fulfill my dreams with you.
Now they want to take my dreams from me.
Now they want me to marry Elcim Hatun.
My Allah, show me a way.
What am I going to choose? The state...
..or my beloved one?
Of course, I love her so much...
..but the state...
The state is greater than
our love, Lord's daughter.
For this state, many people...
...gave up on their lives, their
mothers and their children.
Now I am being tested with my love for you.
For the state...
...let the love of Osman's
son Orhan be sacrificed too.
May the state exist.
-Konur tell me. Did Karasid Bey host you well?
-He did, my Bey.
When people heard that Tajeddin
was beheaded, they started celebrating.
Karasid Bey was pleased and overjoyed.
It's not enough to rejoice together,
will he be with us in the battlefield?
Will he stand behind us when
Olcaytu's army comes? This is important.
He will, my Bey. Not only him...
...I visited all the tribes around.
They are saying that they
will stand behind Osman Bey.
Thank you, thank you.
Thank to them.
-There is another issue.
-What is it?
Too many crusaders ar
coming to the Karasid harbour.
And we don’t know who they
are or where they are coming from.
What happened, Konur Bey? Is
ancient Rome being resurrected?
Do they have swords?
There are no Hatuns and children among
them right? They are coming for a war.
My Bey... Who are they coming for? The Emperor?
No.
For the Executioner of Roman Empire.
We will not let anyone hear this for now.
Orhan. Konur. Get ready.
Go to the harbour. You
need to get news from there.
-Yes my Bey.
My son.
You are just going there to get
news. Don't do anything heroic.
-Okay my Bey.
-Go now.
-Can I come in, my Bey?
-Come in.
My Bey. We found Noyan's helper Abdulkasim.
He is hiding with ten nokers.
We have a lot of things to learn from that dog.
The executioner of Roman Empire is getting ready.
Apparently, he will hurt us badly.
But first, we will go and
get rid of this Mongol issue.
-Inform Gunduz BeyWe will set out.
-Yes my Bey.
Bayindir Bey. How do Turks say?
-You brought joy.
-Thank you, Olivia Hatun.
-Aren't Lords here?
-Not yet. They will all come soon.
They are curious about
the reason of this invitation.
I am also curious. What does
Osman Bey want besides taxes?
When Lords come, you will learn with them.
My Osman... Are you thinking about Orhan?
Tell me Bala.
What do you think about this marriage?
If this marriage happens, there will be unity.
It will be good for all of us.
But...
...Orhan’s heart will be shattered, my Osman.
I know... I know.
Can I come in, my Bey?
-Come in, my son.
I have things to tell you, father.
Mother...
Mother, you will get mad, but...
I want you to
listen to me first.
What happened?
-What happened, my son? Tell me.
-Is this issue...
...about Gonca? I heard she was lost.
Gonca is not lost.
She is here, in the palace.
What are you talking about?
AlaeddinI What is Gonca doing here?
Gonca Hatun...
...yesterday, Gonca Hatun
came to Yenisehir to tell us that...
...Tajeddin came to the marketplace.
-And?
When the assassin woman attacked
me, she threw herself in front of me.
She got injured.
My son... Do you hear what you are saying?
Germiyanoglu Yakup Bey's daughter...
You are saying that she is
here! She is in the palace!
Alaeddin... Alaeddin!
Do you know what it means
for her to be here injured?
Look into my eyes!
I know... I know, my Bey.
But, I had no other choice, father.
Mehmet... told Gonca that he
would kill her if she talked to me.
I couldn’t have said anything
to anyone before I healed her.
Is she alright?
Where is she now?
She was badly injured. But she is alright for now.
She is in Ulgen Hatun's room.
Alaeddin Ali... My son...
...I don't want any secrets in
my palace again, know that.
Know that.
Now go to Mehmet and tell him. Where is Gonca?
My Orhan...
-I was wondering when my mother would come.
I wanted to talk to my son
and have a conversation.
When did you grow up and fight
for our da'wah like a mountain, huh?
Mother... I know what is hiding under your tongue.
You will talk about the marriage issue.
My day, my sun... My brave son.
I know what your he.art wants.
But you are Osman Bey's son.
It is your biggest duty to show
consent to what falls to your share...
...from this dream of a state.
Is it also my duty to have my heart...
...crushed between two stones, mother?
Come... Come here, my son.
My son... You saw Elcim Hatun.
She is very beautiful, smart and wise.
Their lineage suits us, their morals suit us.
She is a Hatun who can enlighten your burden
and stand next to you like a mountain.
Ya... Right, mother?
The Turkmen daughter-in-law you always wanted.
Ah, my Orhan, ah... What matters
is not what your mother wants...
...but the future of our da'wah.
I want what I want for this reason.
Then tell me, mother.
How am I going to accept this when I love...
..Holofira, huh?
How am I going to call anyone else
"my Hatun" besides Holofira, mother?
In our hearts, there is no love greater
than the dream of a state, my son.
There cannot be. Look at us.
Look at me, your father, your Bala mother.
None of us has went through easy challenges.
However, we were a tribe and became a house.
We were a house and became a palace.
To conquer the Wor-ld, we will be challenged.
You will be challenged as well.
Challenges you say..
This is a great challenge, mother.
Besides me..
..with Allah’s permission. I can handle it.
However, Holofira..
How will I come up to her..
..and make her . live with this pain?
The matter of a state dream...
..with two tribes on one hand..
..Holofira and you on the other.
Of course, the last one to decide is Orhan Bey.
However, I know that my
Orhan will make the right decision.
A beautiful on one hand..
..and a state that is above all on the other.
You made us really scared, Gonca.
And Shahzade Alaeddin..
..he was very afraid that
something would happen to you.
It is just remorse, lllgen.
I heard what I heard from him.
-It is enough for me.
-He loves you a lot, Gonca.
He still loves you very much.
This is all because of me.
However, forgive me. I had to, my Gonca.
No, you are not to blame.
Hatuns, Osman Bey is coming.
My daughter. Get well soon, a lot happened to you.
-We've heard.
-I am alright, thank you Osman Bey.
You saved my son’s life. Thank you, Gonca Hatun.
I could not apologize to you properly.
I am sorry, in the name of my
family and what happened before.
It is not right for me to
come to Yenisehir, I know.
However, I was afraid that my
brother would make a mistake.
You did alright, my daughter.
We spoke with your brother as
well. May he prosper if Allah permits.
We owe you a life. The doors
of Yenisehir are open to you.
You are always welcomed here.
Thank you, Osman Bey. I did
nothing compared to what you did.
Take care of yourself.
Your aunt allowed you to take a
breath. However, we can’t stay for long.
-Isn't he Orhan's alp?
-Yes.
Bayindir Beylis inside.
He must've come with him.
That is Imren.
Did Osman Bey made Byzantine
and lords bow down with you?
Yes. You are lucky.
I saw you in peace, not in battle.
Peace is over, don't you know?
It won't start again, until
the very last Kayi dies.
What are you saying? Who are you?
I'm Executioner of Rome, Imren Tegin.
I can't stand this anymore. My
aunt completely lost her mind.
Please help me.
Help me get out of this castle.
Or take my letter to Orhan. Please.
Orhan Bey.
I didn't know about this wedding thing before.
Then you wouldn't want a marriage
with someone you don't know at all, huh?
When it's about the future of two beylics,
....what I want doesn’t matter at all, Orhan Bey.
Then you will accept.
I will do whatever my duty requires. You?
Will you accept if Osman Bey says yes?
While you have someone else in your heart?
Holofira.
-Brother.
Did you make up your mind?
About the marriage?
I am in such a fire, Alaaddin...
...that I’m stuck in it.
Brother.
Osman Bey's sons win all the fights...
...but lose the battle of love, huh?
Will we always lose, brother?
Yes. Yes.
We’re both wounded in the same spot.
But mine is obvious at least.
You're hiding, Alaaddin.
What did you do about Gonca?
-Brother.
-My Shahzade.
We’ll talk later, brother. Later.
Everything is set. We can go.
-Let's go.
-Have a safe journey, brother.
Thank you. Thank you.
Konur Bey.
-My lady.
Just say it, Andra.
Holofira wrote a letter and...
...wanted me to
take it to Orhan Bey.
I didn't want to do anything without asking you.
Won't you give up, Holofira?
-No letters!
-Stop.
Out!
You aren't smart, Olivia.
You're destroying a great chance.
What is in your mind?
What I started with Alaaddin
will be finished with Orhan.
Osman is going to lose one of his sons this time.
Osman Bey, there is the dog.
Gunduz Bey, the dog will survive.
Do whatever you want with the rest. I need him.
I can't forget what he did to my tribe, Osman Bey.
You make him speak.
-But he will be mine in the end.
-It's time. Let's go.
-Alps, attack;
-We're under attack;
My Bey, he's running off;
Where are you going before
you tell me what you know?
Thank you, warriors. Thank you.
Long live. Thank you.
Speak now.
Speak now. Speak!
The Emperor must've
thought about his own interests.
-I want peace.
-You are saying peace, huh, Hatun?
You are saying peace. We do not hurt you...
...because you are Holofira's aunt.
Or, do you think we're unaware of you...
...uniting with the Kite Lord to play games?
-The past is in the past.
-You are right, you are right.
That's why you will prepare
the taxes as soon as possible.
We have no time to wait.
You must be Bayindir.
Yes. Kayi's Bayindir.
Who are you?
The owner of all the castles in these lands.
Olivia I Where are the Lords?
Talk to me, Bayindir.
Ask your questions to me.
I killed all those traitors
with my hands one by one.
-Are you...
-I am.
Executioner of Roman Empire, Imren Tegin.
I will send your dead body
to Osman instead of taxes.
Good then.
I would be pleased. At least, I will be...
..buried in my own lands.
With what sword can you...
...threaten someone whose reunion is shahada...
..infidel?
Your men were not this brave.
They screamed a lot as they died.
You... Did you... kill my valiants?
Infidel!
Osman must have been relieved
after getting rid of Tajeddin Noyan.
But when he learns that I am the actual
trouble for him, he will be out of breath.
But you will not be able to see this.
I will put you in the coffin alive.
Don’t...
Don't you die right away. I don't want
you to die until you are taken to Osman.
What are you going to do now?
I will go to Yenisehir and give Osman his taxes.
So that you are not telling
me, Boran, skin him out!
Stop! Stop! Stop Tajeddin Noyan..
...brought hundreds of weapons from Tabriz.
They were all buried in Kurtmese.
Let me go!
-Are you bargaining now, dog?
That’s all I know.
The things you just said are not
enough to keep you alive. Tell me more.
Tell me.
-Boran!
-Stop! Stop! I will talk;
I will talk! Alright!
There is a big secret!
Look at me... Look at
me... If this secret is big..
..then I will spare your life.
Osman Bey... What are you doing?
Gunduz Bey. Wait.
Come on! -Tajeddin Noyan..
...was meeting with someone for the past few days.
His name is... Turcopole. Turcopole Imren Tegin.
Everyone calls him "the
Executioner of Roman Empire".
Look at me.
Did that Turcopole come here? Huh?
He is here. He killed all the
Lords with his own hands.
And now... he is in Atranos castle.
My Bey... What are we going to do to this dog?
Let him go! Ayaz, Yagiz, take him!
-Send Alps after this dog.
-Okay my Bey.
Bayindir Bey.. Come on. We are going to Yenisehir.
We must prepare the army quickly.
Allah knows that there is
only one love in my heart.
Being a martyr.
And if you allow me...
...I am asking for your prayers for this.
I remembered Abdullah ibn Jahsh's prayer.
Before Uhud, he said to Sa'd ibn Abi Waqqas...
’’You will pray, I will say ’Aameen’...
...I will pray, and you will say ’Aameen’...
...so our Allah can accept our
prayers." Sa'd ibn Abi Waqqas...
...prayed to fight all the
infidels, get wounded...
...and become a martyr.
Abdullah ibn Jahsh said "Aameen"...
...and he prayed: 'Send me...
...strong infidels to fight and...
...defeat, then let one of
them come and martyr me.
May they cut off my mouth, nose, and ears.
When my Allah asks ’where are your limbs?'...
...will say I committed many sins with them...
...and I was ashamed to
stand before You with them."
Sa'd ibn Abi Waqqas unintentionally said...
.."amen".
-His prayer was accepted.
-I have many sins as well.
May Allah..
...grant me with martyrdom...
...when He forgives me.
You're praying like a lover.
Thank you.
Lovers don't die, they are eternal...
...because their souls belong to Allah.
She's strong.
Praise be!
It seems GmbH she trained herself well!
You seem to like that, mother.
Malhun Hatun. I didn't see you, sorry,
Don't even mention it, dear.
But you looked angry.
Are you angry because of the marriage matter?
If you're here to talk about this...
No. I wanted to see you, in fact.
But as far as I see, you
don't want this marriage, huh?
-You have someone in your heart?
-No.
I didn't have time to deal
with love affairs, Malhun Hatun.
Since I left my mother, I’ve
carried my tribe's burden.
As for the marriage,
...I've heard that your son
has another woman in his heart.
I don't want to be the hatun of
a man who loves someone else.
It means you don't want this marriage, huh?
If I were only Elcim, no.
I would never marry your son.
But I’m Efendize Elcim Hatun, a Bey's daughter.
I'll do whatever I need to do for my tribe.
Will I hurt my pride? Yes.
I will have to accept this marriage
with a bleeding heart, Malhun Hatun.
I feel so upset when I see you like this.
Just let me tell Shahzade
Alaaddin that you are innocent.
No need for that. He didn't
believe my words, Ulgen.
Gonca Hatun, alps are ready.
They'll escort you to the frontier market.
Ulgen can go with you if you like.
No need. Thanks, Alaaddin Bey.
Ointment. Apply this on your wounds.
No need.I can cure my own wound.
You shouldn't have got one more
wound because of me, Gonca Hatun.
-Does it hurt much?
-If I had a life, I might feel it.
Compared to my suffering, this is nothing.
My heart burns so much..
...that I feel no other pain but this.
Who?
Who made that fire?
-Is it my fault?
-No.
I don't blame you.
It was my mistake.
I just overestimated this love, Alaaddin.
I don’t know.
’’Scholar will understand and believe me.”
"He’ll see my
suffering", I thought.
"He won't leave me alone", I thought.
I never left you alone.
You know nothing, Alaaddin. Nothing at all.
You know nothing about my sufferings.
Do you know why I stayed away from you?
You don't.
Because it was easy for you to blame me, right?
Gonca, don't..
You left me alone, Alaaddin.
Just over there, you said it’s over.
You said you silenced your heart.
You even couldn’t say my name, remember?
That day, I killed Trickster Hatun.
What are you saying?
It's not over...
It’s over, Alaaddin Bey.
What is over in your heart
is over in my heart too.
Gonca.
Don't do this.
Aladdin!
Alaaddin! Come out, Alaaddin!
Aladdin! Get out Aladdin!
Gonca...
You stay back. He must be furious now.
Come out!
Come out, Alaaddin!
Easy, Mehmed! Easy!
Are you a just trouble for us?
Will you bring nothing but
troubles? Where is Gonca?
Alps, stay back; Mehmed, pull yourself together;
How many more times should my
sister get wounded because of you?
Brother; Stop.
-I will kill you, Alaaddin!
-Brother, stop!
Alps, what are you waiting for? Hold him
-Pull yourself together!
-I will kill you!
Get off! Get off!
Enough! Pull yourself
together, Mehmed Bey!
Gonca saved Alaaddin’s life.
And Alaaddin saved you all,
remember? Your father, you and others...
Pull yourself together.
I will kill you, Alaaddin.
-I will kill you!
-Enough; Stop, brother!
How can you defend himi
Isn't your life worth anything?
We will talk about it in
marketplace. Now stop it, please.
I will kill you Alaeddin!
You won't see each other again!
Let it be heard! If you see each other again..
..I swear I will kill you Alaeddin!
Your power is only enough to
make empty threats, Mehmed!
Enough; It is over I said!
Let him go!
Come on, move!
Come on, walk!
Come on!
-Boran.
-My Bey.
Prepare the war equipment.
-We will walk to Adraneia.
-As you command, my Bey.
Alps! We will siege Adraneia
Bayindir Bey is at the hands of
Executioner of Rome, we will take him back.
Osman Bey. What is it, Osman Bey?
If we do not move fast, bad things will happen.
My Bey!
My Bey. Someone came..
-They want to see you.
-Who is it?
He says that he is the leader of lords.
-What is his name?
-He says it is "Turkopol Imren Tegin".
-What?
-"Turkopol Imren Tegin".
Imren Tegin you say.
The Executioner of Rome.
So he acted faster than us.
Let him come.
Open the gates.
-Osman Bey.
-What do want?
I got news from the Emperor.
You killed his daughter, Princess Maria.
The issues you have with
Mongols do not concern us.
You will pay the price of Princess' death.
Look here! Look here!
I will ask you just once.
Turkopol dog or whatever you are..
Where is Bayindir?
You killed The Emperor of Rome's daughter.
My duty is to have her vengeance.
What about the vengeance of your house?
The State of Seljuks has
fallen because of your treachery!
States rise, states fall.
I chose to serve myself, not to states.
If something happens to Bayindir Bey..
..then you will see what vengeance is.
I will be your enemy until the end.
Osman Bey. I am came here to declare you..
...a war that won't end until one of us dies.
However, the war has just been declared.
That is why, I will hand you your
previous taxes and Bayindir Bey.
Turkopols always keep their promises.
My Bey, byzantians are bringing the taxes.
Let them in.
Bring them down!
Open it!
Kara Ali...
-He is still alive, my Bey.
-Bayindir!
“Come on, get him up!
-Come on!
-Hold him!
-I got him!
Bayindir! Who did this to you, brother.
Who? Alaeddin, prepare the room!
Alaeddin, why are you standing around? Come on;!
-My Bey.
-My Glorious Bey.
Listen to me.
I was born as a Cavundur..
..and depart as a Kayi.
-There is no departing, Bayindir.
-My Bey..
There is nothing left to do now.
This body I tired..
..will be delivered to Allah
with proud, thanks to you.
-Bayindir..
-Give me your blessing.
Of course, of course..
Of course I give you my blessing.
I give you, of course..
I bear witness that there is none
worthy of worship except Allah...
and I bear witness that Muhammad
(PBUH) is His servant and Messenger.
"Indeed, to Allah we belong
and to Allah we shall return."
Do not worry.
I swear to you..
..we will drown them in their own blood.
Bury your martyrs.
Prepare the army.
We will bury those who did this under this earth
It's time for war!
Visit turkision.com for more!